Finding Aid for Michigan Daily Records, 1950-2006
Bentley Historical Library
- Faculty, Staff, Administrators-Biographical Files, 5 linear feet
  - T-Z
    - Taylor, William B. -- Medicine (Box 17)
    - Taylor, William R. -- Botany (Box 17)
    - Teal, Laurence L. -- Wind Instruments (Box 17)
    - Thomas, Edwin J. -- Social Work (Box 17)
    - Thomas, Norman C. -- Political Science (Box 17)
    - Thomas, Morgan -- Political Science (Box 17)
    - Thomassen, Lars -- Chemical Engineering (Box 17)
    - Thrall, Robert M. -- Math (Box 17)
    - Throop, Palmer A. -- History (Box 17)
    - Thuma, Burton D. -- Asst. Dean, LSA (Box 17)
    - Tikofsky, Ronald S. -- Speech (Box 17)
    - Tilly, Charles -- Social Science, History, Sociology (Box 17)
    - Tinkle, Donald W. -- Ecology, Evolutionary Biology (Box 17)
    - Tirrell, John E. -- Alumni Association (Box 17)
    - Titiev, Mischa -- Anthropology (Box 17)
    - Titus, Helen M. -- Piano (Box 17)
    - Tompa, Alex S. -- Ecology, Evolutionary Biology (Box 17)
    - Tonsor, Stephen J. -- History (Box 17)
    - Tourtellotte, Wallace E. -- Neurology (Box 17)
    - Townsend, Leroy -- Medical researcher (Box 17)
    - Townsend, Richard E. -- Chemical Engineering (Box 17)
    - Towsley, Harry A. -- Pediatrics (Box 17)
    - Tracy, John E. -- Law (Box 17)
    - Troth, Eugene W. -- Music Education (Box 17)
    - Trow, William C. -- Education (Box 17)
    - Trytten, John M. -- Business Education (Box 17)
    - Tupper, Charles John -- Internal Medicine (Box 17)
    - Turneaure, Frederick S. -- Geology (Box 17)
    - Uhlenbeck, George E. -- Physics (Box 17)
    - Umiker, William O. -- Pathology (Box 17)
    - Valusek, John E. -- Reading Improvement, Education, Psychological Srvcs (Box 17)
    - Vance, Kenneth E. -- Consultant (Box 17)
    - Van den Broek, Jan -- Engineering (Box 17)
    - Vandermade, Minor, Jr. -- University Hospital (Box 17)
    - Van der Schalie, Henry -- Zoology (Box 17)
    - Van Vlack, Lawrence H. -- Metallurgical Eng (Box 17)
    - Van Wylen, Gordon J. -- Mechanical Eng (Box 17)
    - Varner, Nellie -- Regent (Box 17)
    - Vaughan, Henry F. -- Public Health (Box 17)
    - Veltman, Martinus J. G. -- Physics (Box 17)
    - Velz, Clarence J. -- Public Health (Box 17)
    - Vial, Alexander B. -- Surgery (Box 17)
    - Vidar, Frede J. -- Drawing (Box 17)
    - Vincent, Donald E. -- Library, Dearborn (Box 17)
    - Vincent, Edward T. -- Engineering (Box 17)
    - Vines, Quentin C. -- Mechanical Eng (Box 17)
    - Vinter, Robert D. -- Social Work (Box 17)
    - Virtue, Maxine B. -- Social Work (Box 17)
    - Voss, Edward G. -- Botany (Box 17)
    - Vroman, Clyde -- Music Education, Admissions (Box 17)
    - Waggoner, Raymond W. -- Psychiatry (Box 17)
    - Wagman, Frederick H. -- Library Science (Box 17)
    - Wagner, Herbert P. -- Food Service (Box 17)
    - Wallner, Julius Michael -- Psychiatry (Box 17)
    - Walter, Erich A. -- English, Asst. to President (Box 17)
    - Ward, Peter -- Pathology, Dean of Med. School (Box 17)
    - Warner, Robert A. -- Music (Box 17)
    - Warren, Don W. -- Math (Box 17)
    - Warshaw, Martin R. -- Marketing (Box 17)
    - Waterman, Merwin H. -- Finance (Box 17)
    - Watkins, Herbert G. -- Secretary, Asst. Vice President (Box 17)
    - Weaver, Bennett -- English (Box 17)
    - Weaver, Richard L. -- Conservation (Box 17)
    - Weeks, Robert P. -- English (Box 17)
    - Wegman, Myron E. -- Dean, Public Health (Box 17)
    - Weichlein, William J. -- Music Literature (Box 17)
    - Weimar, John -- English (Box 17)
    - Weintraub, Daniel -- Psychology (Box 17)
    - Weinberg, Gerhard -- History (Box 17)
    - Wellman, Richard V. -- Law (Box 17)
    - Wells, Carlton F. -- English (Box 17)
    - Wentzel, Donat G. -- Astronomy (Box 17)
    - Wernette, John P. -- Business Admin (Box 17)
    - Westerman, Walter S., Jr. -- Education (Box 17)
    - White, Ink -- Regent (Box 17)
    - White, John P. -- Political Science (Box 17)
    - Wehrer, Joseph J. -- Arch. & Design (Box 17)
    - White, Leslie A. -- Anthropology (Box 17)
    - White, Robert R. -- Chemical Engineering (Box 17)
    - Whitehouse, Walter M. -- Radiology (Box 17)
    - Whiting, Allen -- Political Science (Box 17)
    - Whitman, Elmer L. -- Dentistry (Box 17)
    - Whittemore, Harlow O. -- Architecture (Box 17)
    - Wiesner, Jerome B. -- Political Science (Box 18)
    - Wilder, Raymond L. -- Math (Box 18)
    - Wilensky, Harold L. -- Sociology (Box 18)
    - Willcox, William B. -- History (Box 18)
    - Willson, Robert -- Gynecology, Obstetrics (Box 18)
    - Wilson, Gayle C. -- Admissions (Box 18)
    - Wilson, James L. -- Pediatrics (Box 18)
    - Wilson, James Tinley -- Geology, IST (Box 18)
    - Wilt, Richard -- Art (Box 18)
    - Wingo, Glenn Max -- Education (Box 18)
    - Winner, Thomas G. -- Slavic Languages (Box 18)
    - Withey, Stephen B. -- Psychology (Box 18)
    - Woodburne, Russell T. -- Anatomy (Box 18)
    - Woodcock, Leonard -- Political Science (Box 18)
    - Woods, Lauren Albert -- Pharmacology (Box 18)
    - Woodworth, G. Walter -- Business Admin (Box 18)
    - Work, Walter P. -- Medical (Box 18)
    - Wright, Lafayette Hart -- Law (Box 18)
    - Wyatt, Frederick -- Psychology (Box 18)
    - Wyllie, Cleland B. -- Info. & News Service (Box 18)
    - Wynne, Michael J. -- Botany (Box 18)
    - Xu, Lian-cang -- Psychology (Box 18)
    - Yamagiwa, Joseph Koshimi -- Japanese (Box 18)
    - Yates, Edward A. -- Mechanical Eng (Box 18)
    - Yntema, Hessel E. -- Comparative Law (Box 18)
    - Yocum, Charles F. -- Biology (Box 18)
    - Yocum, Conrad S. -- ? (Box 18)
    - Young, Leigh J. -- Silviculture (Box 18)
    - Youtie, Herbert C. -- Papyrology (Box 18)
    - Youtz, Philip N. -- Dean of Arch. & Des (Box 18)
    - Zander, Alvin F. -- Educational Psych (Box 18)
    - Zeigler, Thornton W. -- Psychiatry and Neuropsychiatric Institute (Box 18)
    - Zeisler, Karl F. -- Journalism (Box 18)
    - Zimmerman, William -- Political Science (Box 18)
    - Zuidema, George D. -- Medical School (Box 18)
    - Zumberge, James H. -- Geology (Box 18)
- Faculty, Staff, Administrators - Photographs
  The Faculty, Staff, Administrators - Photographs series is comprised of black and white, positive prints, of varying sizes, the majority of which are portraits. The series is arranged alphabetically by surname and includes the department(s) in which the individual worked.
  - A-C
    - Abbott, Herbert B. -- ? (Box 19)
    - Akerman, Joseph R. -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Alexander, Richard D. -- Zoology (Box 19)
    - Allen, John M. -- Zoology (Box 19)
    - Allison, Alexander -- English (Box 19)
    - Allmand, Charles M. -- Personnel at U-Hospital (Box 19)
    - Alvord, Herbert H. -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Anderson, Leigh -- Chemistry (Box 19)
    - Anderson, Lester W. -- Education (Box 19)
    - Angell, Robert -- Sociology (Box 19)
    - Arpaci, Vedat S. -- Mechanical Eng (Box 19)
    - Arthos, John -- English (Box 19)
    - Atkinson, John W. -- Psychology (Box 19)
    - Axelrod, Solomon J. -- Public Health, -- Economics (Box 19)
    - Bader, Arno L. -- English (Box 19)
    - Bailey, John -- Near Eastern Language & Lit (Box 19)
    - Baird, Claribel -- Speech (Box 19)
    - Baker, Burton L. -- Anatomy (Box 19)
    - Baker, Dean C. -- Journalism (Box 19)
    - Baker, Sheridan W., Jr. -- English (Box 19)
    - Ballis, William J. -- Political Science (Box 19)
    - Barker, H. Kenneth -- Bureau of Appts (Box 19)
    - Barlow, Robin -- Economics (Box 19)
    - Baromeo, Chase -- Music (Box 19)
    - Bates, Marston -- Zoology (Box 19)
    - Beach, Lowell W. -- Education (Box 19)
    - Beardsley, Richard K. -- Anthropology (Box 19)
    - Beckett, Morley B. -- Health Service (Box 19)
    - Beierwaltes, William H. -- Medicine (Box 19)
    - Bender, Leonard F. -- Medicine (Box 19)
    - Benedict, Milbry "Moby" -- Baseball Coach (Box 19)
    - Benford, Harry B. -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Berry, Ralph M. -- Civil Engineering (Box 19)
    - Berry, Wallace T. -- Music School (Box 19)
    - Bishop, William Warner, Jr. -- Law (Box 19)
    - Blatt, Josef -- Music (Box 19)
    - Bloomer, H. Harlan -- Speech (Box 19)
    - Bolt, Jay A. -- Mechanical Eng (Box 19)
    - Bonk, Wallace J. -- Library Science (Box 19)
    - Bordin, Edward S. -- Psychology (Box 19)
    - Bossart, R. Eugene -- Music (Box 19)
    - Bostian, Dr. -- ? (Box 19)
    - Bowditch, John III -- History (Box 19)
    - Bowman, Robert A. -- Public Health (Box 19)
    - Boyce, Ernest -- Civil Engineering (Box 19)
    - Boys, Richard C. -- English (Box 19)
    - Brablec, Carl -- Regent (Box 19)
    - Brandt, Carl G. -- English (Box 19)
    - Brater, Ernest F. -- Civil Engineering (Box 19)
    - Braun, Frank X. -- German (Box 19)
    - Brazer, Harvey E. -- Economics (Box 19)
    - Bredvold, Louis I. -- English (Box 19)
    - Briggs, Louis I., Jr. -- Geology (Box 19)
    - Briggs, Robert P. -- Vice President, Regent (Box 19)
    - Brigham, George B., Jr. -- Architecture (Box 19)
    - Britton, Allen P. -- Music (Box 19)
    - Bromage, Arthur W. -- Political Science (Box 19)
    - Bromage, Mary C. -- Business Admin (Box 19)
    - Browder, Olin L. -- Law (Box 19)
    - Brown, Deming B. -- Slavic Dept (Box 19)
    - Brown, Dugald E. S. -- Zoology (Box 19)
    - Brown, George G. -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Brown, Gerald S. -- History (Box 19)
    - Brown, Gordon C. -- Epidemiology, Public Health (Box 19)
    - Brown, Morton -- Math (Box 19)
    - Brownell, Lloyd E. -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Brumfiel, Charles E. -- Math (Box 19)
    - Bull, Hempstead S. -- Electrical Eng (Box 19)
    - Burckhalter, J. H. -- Pharmacy (Box 19)
    - Burroughs, Robert E. -- Research Admin (Box 19)
    - Burt, William H. -- Zoology (Box 19)
    - Butsch, Robert S. -- Exhibit Museum (Box 19)
    - Buttrey, T. -- Classical Studies (Box 19)
    - Byrn, Delmont K. -- Education (Box 19)
    - Caddell, Robert M. -- Mechanical Eng (Box 19)
    - Cain, Stanley -- Conservation (Box 19)
    - Campbell, Angus -- Psychology, SRC (Box 19)
    - Cameron, George G. -- Near Eastern Studies (Box 19)
    - Cannell, Charles F. -- Psych. in Journalism (Box 19)
    - Carduner, Jean R. -- French (Box 19)
    - Carey, John J. -- Electrical Eng (Box 19)
    - Carey, William J. -- Business Admin (Box 19)
    - Carow, John -- Forest Management (Box 19)
    - Carpenter, Finley -- Education (Box 19)
    - Carruth, Hayden -- Speech (Box 19)
    - Carter, Paul D. -- Education (Box 19)
    - Cartwright, Dorwin P. -- Psychology (Box 19)
    - Case, Kenneth -- Physics (Box 19)
    - Cassara, Frank -- Arch. & Design (Box 19)
    - Cavender, George R. -- Music (Box 19)
    - Cesari, Lamberte -- Math (Box 19)
    - Chambers, Walter L. -- Architecture (Box 19)
    - Chandler, David C. -- Zoology (Box 19)
    - Charbeneau, Gerald T. -- Dentistry (Box 19)
    - Child, Charles G. -- Medicine (Box 19)
    - Choate, Robert A. -- Law (Box 19)
    - Christensen, Halvor N. -- Medicine (Box 19)
    - Church, Michael P. -- Extension Office (Box 19)
    - Clark, John -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Cohen, Wilbur -- Dean of Education (Box 19)
    - Collins, Morgan -- Finance (Box 19)
    - Conard, Alfred F. -- Law (Box 19)
    - Conn, Jerome W. -- Medicine (Box 19)
    - Connable, Alfred B. -- Regent (Box 19)
    - Coombs, Clyde H. -- Psychology (Box 19)
    - Coon, Minor J. -- Biological Chemistry (Box 19)
    - Cooperrider, Luke K. -- Law (Box 19)
    - Copi, Irving M. -- Philosophy (Box 19)
    - Copley, Frank O. -- Latin (Box 19)
    - Cortright, Donald N. -- Civil Engineering (Box 19)
    - Couch, Richard B. -- Naval Architecture (Box 19)
    - Courte, Robert & wife -- Music (Box 19)
    - Courtney, C. B. -- Dearborn Center (Box 19)
    - Cowan, Donald R. G. -- Marketing (Box 19)
    - Craine, Lyle E. -- Conservation (Box 19)
    - Crane, Horace R. -- Physics (Box 19)
    - Crane, Verner W. -- American History (Box 19)
    - Crary, Douglas D. -- Geography (Box 19)
    - Crichton, Mary C. -- Germany (Box 19)
    - Crisler, Fritz -- Athletic Director (Box 19)
    - Cudlip, William B. -- Regent (Box 19)
    - Crump, James I., Jr. -- Chinese (Box 19)
    - Cutler, Richard L. -- Vice President (Box 19)
    - Cuyler, Louise -- Music (Box 19)
  - D-G
    - Dalley, Orien E. -- Music, WUOM (Box 19)
    - Davenport, Elizabeth -- Acting Dean of Women (Box 19)
    - Davenport, Fred M. -- Public Health (Box 19)
    - Davis, H. Chandler -- ? (Box 19)
    - Dawson, William R. -- Zoology (Box 19)
    - Debler, Walter R. -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Densmore, G. E. -- Speech (Box 19)
    - Dexter, Benning W. -- Piano (Box 19)
    - Diamond, Howard -- Electrical Eng (Box 19)
    - Dice, Lee R. -- Zoology (Box 19)
    - Dickens, William B. -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Dickinson, David G. -- Pediatrics (Box 19)
    - Dimond, Stanley E. -- Education (Box 19)
    - Dingman, Reed O. -- Dentistry (Box 19)
    - Dixon, Robert L., Jr. -- Business Admin (Box 19)
    - Domino, Edward F. -- Pharmacology (Box 19)
    - Donahue, Wilma T. -- Psychology (Box 19)
    - Dorr, Harold M. -- Administration (Box 19)
    - Dow, William G. -- Electrical Eng (Box 19)
    - Duey, Philip A. -- Voice (Box 19)
    - Dumond, Dwight L. -- History (Box 19)
    - Dunham, Arthur -- Social Work (Box 19)
    - Dunham, Arthur L. -- History (Box 19)
    - Easlick, Kenneth A. -- Dentistry (Box 19)
    - Eastman, Arthur M. -- English (Box 19)
    - Eckert, Otto E. -- Regent (Box 19)
    - Eckstein, Alexander -- Economics (Box 19)
    - Eckstein, Henry C. -- Biological Chemistry (Box 19)
    - Edel, Oliver A. -- Violin/Cello (Box 19)
    - Eder, George -- Business Admin (Box 19)
    - Edmondson, Glenn V. -- Mechanical Eng (Box 19)
    - Edwards, Rev. J. Edgar -- Guild House (Box 19)
    - Efimenco, Marbury -- Political Science (Box 19)
    - Ehrmann, Howard M. -- History (Box 19)
    - Eichelberger, Maurice B. -- Engin. Drawing (Box 19)
    - Eisenberg, Marvin J. -- History of Art (Box 19)
    - Eisley, Joe G. -- Aeronautical Eng (Box 19)
    - Eitman, Wilford -- Business Admin (Box 19)
    - Eldersveld, Samuel J. -- Political Science (Box 19)
    - Eley, Lynn W. -- Political Science, Extension Service (Box 19)
    - Elgass, George A. -- Marketing (Box 19)
    - Eliot, Johan W. -- Public Health (Box 19)
    - Else, Gerald F. -- Greek, Latin (Box 19)
    - Elving, Philip J. -- Chemistry (Box 19)
    - Emmons, Ardath -- Phoenix Project (Box 19)
    - Emmons, Walter J. -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Engel, Edwin A. -- English (Box 19)
    - Enns, John Hermann -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Epple, Arnet B. -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Erazmus, Edward T. -- English Lang. Inst (Box 19)
    - Erbe, Wesley A. -- Consultant in Ed (Box 19)
    - Ericksen, Stanford C. -- Psychology (Box 19)
    - Eschman, Donald F. -- Geology (Box 19)
    - Estep, Jeannette Floyd (Mrs. Samuel) -- Sec. of Intercoll. Athletics, Dir. of Women's Glee Club (Box 19)
    - Estep, Samuel -- Law (Box 19)
    - Etter, Lester F. -- Intercoll. Athletics (Box 19)
    - Evaldson, Rune L. -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Farris, Hansford W. -- Electrical Eng (Box 19)
    - Feather, Norman T. -- Psychology (Box 19)
    - Feingold, Eugene -- Political Science (Box 19)
    - Felheim, Marvin -- English (Box 19)
    - Feuerwerker, Albert -- History (Box 19)
    - Field, John V. -- Journalism (Box 19)
    - Fifield, Russell H. -- Political Science (Box 19)
    - Finch, Stuart M. -- Psychiatry (Box 19)
    - Fischer, Carl H. -- Business Admin (Box 19)
    - Fitts, Paul Morris, Jr. -- Psychology (Box 19)
    - Flanders, Ned -- Education (Box 19)
    - Fleming, Robben -- President (Box 19)
    - Flood, Merrill M. -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Flower, John A. -- Music Theory (Box 19)
    - Follo, Charles L. -- Extension (Box 19)
    - Fontanna, Stanley G. -- Natural Resources (Box 19)
    - Ford, Robert S. -- Dean of Rackham,Economics (Box 19)
    - Forsyth, George H. -- Fine Arts (Box 19)
    - Foster, Morris -- Zoology (Box 19)
    - Fouts, Jack -- Physical Education, Coach (Box 19)
    - Fox, Robert S. -- Education (Box 19)
    - Fralick, F. Bruce -- Ophthalmology (Box 19)
    - Francis, Thomas, Jr. -- Epidemiology (Box 19)
    - Franken, Peter -- ? (Box 19)
    - Frankena, William -- Philosophy (Box 19)
    - Frederick, Julian R. -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Freedman, Ronald -- Sociology (Box 19)
    - Freehling, William -- History (Box 19)
    - French, David M. -- Flint College (Box 19)
    - French, Esther L. -- Physical Education (Box 19)
    - Freud, Clarice -- Social Work (Box 19)
    - Fricke, Benno G. -- Psych. & Exam Srvc (Box 19)
    - Friedman, Robert S. -- Political Science (Box 19)
    - Fries, Charles C. -- English (Box 19)
    - Fritz, Irving B. -- Physiology (Box 19)
    - Fuller, Elsie R. -- Dean (Box 19)
    - Furstenberg, Albert C. -- Otolaryngology (Box 19)
    - Gabarty, Thomas -- English (Box 19)
    - Gable, William R. -- Public Admin (Box 19)
    - Gamson, William -- Sociology (Box 19)
    - Gannon, John L. -- Public Health (Box 19)
    - Garbutt, Jack A. -- Drawing, Painting (Box 19)
    - Gardner, Wallace W. -- Business Admin (Box 19)
    - Garrison, Garnet R. -- Television (Box 19)
    - Gault, Edgar H. -- Marketing (Box 19)
    - George, B. James, Jr. -- Law (Box 19)
    - Gerard, Ralph W. -- Neurophysiology (Box 19)
    - Gerhardt, Philipp -- Bacteriology (Box 19)
    - Gerlach, Dr. Arch C. -- ? (Box 19)
    - Gessner, Quenten -- Extension Service (Box 19)
    - Getting, Vlado A. -- Public Health (Box 19)
    - Gibson, William Charles -- Public Health (Box 19)
    - Gies, Thomas G. -- Finance (Box 19)
    - Gilbert, Edward & Elmer -- Aeronautical Eng (Box 19)
    - Gillis, Donald -- Vice President, National Music Camp (Box 19)
    - Gindin, James J. -- English (Box 19)
    - Gjelsness, Rudolph H. -- Library Science (Box 19)
    - Glaser, Donald A. -- Physics (Box 19)
    - Glasser, Paul H. -- Social Work (Box 19)
    - Glicksberg, Daniel H. -- English Lang. Inst (Box 19)
    - Glysson, Eugene A. -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Goddard, Edwin N. -- Geology (Box 19)
    - Goebel, Paul G. -- Board of Regents (Box 19)
    - Goldberg, David -- Social & Pub. Health (Box 19)
    - Goldberg, Leo -- Astronomy (Box 19)
    - Gomberg, Henry J. -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Gooch, Donald B. -- Design (Box 19)
    - Goode, Harry H. -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Gordon, Jesse E. -- Psychology (Box 19)
    - Gordon, Kenneth F. -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Gore, George J. -- ? (Box 19)
    - Gores, Walter J. -- ? (Box 19)
    - Gosling, Glenn D. -- University Press (Box 19)
    - Gosling, L. A. Peter -- Geography (Box 19)
    - Grabar, Oleg -- Near East Art (Box 19)
    - Grace, Frank -- Political Science (Box 19)
    - Graf, Otto -- Honors Council (Box 19)
    - Graham, Bruce D. -- Medicine (Box 19)
    - Graham, Samuel A. -- Zoology (Box 19)
    - Graham, Stanley K. -- U-M Publications (Box 19)
    - Grassmuck, George L. -- Political Science (Box 19)
    - Graves, William H. -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Gray, Whitmore -- Law (Box 19)
    - Green, Elizabeth -- Music Education (Box 19)
    - Greenhut, Morris -- English (Box 19)
    - Greenman, Emerson F. -- Anthropology (Box 19)
    - Greenshields, Bruce -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Greenwood, Donald T. -- Aeronautical Eng (Box 19)
    - Greey, George -- Physical Education (Box 19)
    - Greer, Frances -- Voice (Box 19)
    - Grew, Raymond -- History (Box 19)
    - Griffin, James B. -- Archaeology (Box 19)
    - Griffith, R. -- Investment Officer (Box 19)
    - Grimes, Dale M. -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Groesbeck, Byron L. -- Admissions (Box 19)
    - Groesbeck, Edward G. -- Administration (Box 19)
    - Grossbard, Steven -- Teaching Fellow (Box 19)
    - Guarino, Armand J. -- Biological Chemistry (Box 19)
    - Gustafson, Felix G. -- Botany (Box 19)
  - H-K
    - Haddock, Fred T. -- Eng., Astronomy (Box 19)
    - Hakken, Howard G. -- University Architect (Box 19)
    - Halford, Joseph O. -- Chemistry (Box 19)
    - Hall, John W. -- Japanese studies, History (Box 19)
    - Hall, Keith W. -- Mechanical Eng (Box 19)
    - Hall, Robert B. -- Geography (Box 19)
    - Halmos, Paul R. -- Math (Box 19)
    - Halpern, Edward -- Math (Box 19)
    - Halstead, William P. -- Speech (Box 19)
    - Hammitt, Frederick G. -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Hancock, Walton M. -- Industrial Eng (Box 19)
    - Hann, Arthur S. -- Business Admin (Box 19)
    - Hansen, Arthur G. -- Mechanical Eng (Box 19)
    - Hansen, Holger M. -- Eng. Mechanics (Box 19)
    - Hanson, Russell G. -- International Center (Box 19)
    - Hardman, Harold F. -- Pharmacology (Box 19)
    - Harris, Robert -- Law (Box 19)
    - Harris, Robert B. -- Civil Engineering (Box 19)
    - Harrison, George B. -- English (Box 19)
    - Harrison, Saul I. -- Children's Hospital (Box 19)
    - Hartman, Francis A. -- Firemanship Training (Box 19)
    - Harvey, William B. -- Law (Box 19)
    - Haber, William -- Economics, Dean of LSA (Box 19)
    - Hauenstein, Nelson M. -- Music (Box 19)
    - Haugh, Harold -- Music (Box 19)
    - Haugh, Robert Fulton -- English (Box 19)
    - Haun, Eugene -- Residence Halls (Box 19)
    - Hawley, Amos H. -- Sociology (Box 19)
    - Hawkins, Carl S. -- Law (Box 19)
    - Hay, George E. -- Math (Box 19)
    - Hayes, Douglas A. -- Finance (Box 19)
    - Hayes, Samuel P. -- ? (Box 19)
    - Hays, William -- Dean of LSA (Box 19)
    - Hazen, Wayne E. -- Physics (Box 19)
    - Heady, Chester Ferrel, Jr. -- Political Science (Box 19)
    - Heimbach, Clinton L. -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Heinrich, Eberhardt W. -- Mineralogy (Box 19)
    - Hellwarth, Arlen R. -- Asst. Dean of Engineering (Box 19)
    - Henderson, Algo D. -- Education (Box 19)
    - Henderson, John W. -- Medicine (Box 19)
    - Henle, Paul -- Philosophy (Box 19)
    - Heppinstall, Robert S. -- Engin, Drawing (Box 19)
    - Hepworth, Samuel R. -- Accounting (Box 19)
    - Herbert, Ralph -- Music (Box 19)
    - Heusal, Albert E. -- Security Officer (Box 19)
    - Hewson, E. Wendell -- Meteorology (Box 19)
    - Hibbard, Claude W. -- Geology (Box 19)
    - Hicks, Aubrey -- UMRI (Box 19)
    - Hildebrandt, Herbert W. -- Speech (Box 19)
    - Hildebrandt, Theophil H. -- Math (Box 19)
    - Hill, Donald -- English (Box 19)
    - Hill, L. Clayton -- Industrial Relations (Box 19)
    - Hill, Lawrence -- Hospital Admin (Box 19)
    - Himler, Leonard E. -- Mental Health (Box 19)
    - Hinds, Richard J. -- University Hospital (Box 19)
    - Hitchcock, H. Wiley -- Music (Box 19)
    - Hoad, William C. -- Civil Engineering (Box 19)
    - Hoad, William M. -- Small Business (Box 19)
    - Hoard, Robert -- Piano (Box 19)
    - Hobbs, William -- Geology (Box 19)
    - Hodges, Fred J. -- Radiology (Box 19)
    - Hodges, Lewis H. -- Education (Box 19)
    - Hoisington, Robert H. -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Hok, Ruth C. -- English Lang. Inst (Box 19)
    - Holland, Lewis N. -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Holland, William J. -- Health (Box 19)
    - Holton, Raymond W. -- Botany (Box 19)
    - Holz, Emil A. -- Music (Box 19)
    - Hood, Marguerite V. -- Music Education (Box 19)
    - Hooper, Emmet T. -- Museum (Box 19)
    - Hord, Robert -- Piano (Box 19)
      (see Hord)
    - Horton, Robert J. M. -- Epidemiology (Box 19)
    - Hourani, George F. -- Arabic studies (Box 19)
    - Housel, William S. -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Howard, Rev. -- University Hospital (Box 19)
    - Howard, William E. -- Astronomy (Box 19)
    - Howe, Robert M. -- Engineering (Box 19)
    - Howe, Thalia -- Visiting Professor (Box 19)
    - Howell, Roger W. -- Public Health (Box 19)
    - Hubbell, Theodore H. -- Zoology (Box 19)
    - Hucker, Charles -- Far Eastern Language and Literature (Box 19)
    - Hughes, Byron O. -- Child Development (Box 19)
    - Hulslander, Stewart C. -- Education (Box 19)
    - Hunsicker, Paul A. -- Physical Education (Box 19)